BACK IN THE '80s AND '90s,
INFORMATION WAS KEY.
BUT NOW IT'S A WHOLE NEW GAME.
THESE DAYS, WITH THE INTERNET,
TWO FRESH GRADS SITTING
IN SOME SHIT WINDOWLESS BOX
MIGHT BE PUSHING AROUND MORE MONEY
THAN SOME OF THE BIGGEST FUNDS,
AND GETTING INFORMATION
FASTER THAN ANYONE ELSE
BECAUSE THEY'RE MASTERS
OF A CHAT ROOM.
THAT'S WHY OUR JOB
IS NOT JUST ABOUT INFORMATION;
IT'S ABOUT INTELLIGENCE.
WHEN WE BUY A STOCK,
IT'S BECAUSE AN IDIOT
SOLD IT TO US.
AND WHEN I SAY US,
I DON'T MEAN THOSE PUSSIES
OVER ON WALL STREET.
HEDGE FUNDS, GENTLEMEN,
ARE THE FUTURE.
AND WE THRIVE NOT ONLY BY OUR ABILITY
TO DECIPHER THE CLUES,
AND READ BETWEEN THE LINES,
BUT BY DESIGNING FOOLPROOF PLANS
TO BE EXECUTED TO THE 'T'
BY SUPERCAPITALISTS.
WE ARE A SUPERIOR,
COVERT AGENCY OF OPERATIVES
CREATED AND INCENTIVIZED
TO FULFILL ONE MISSION:
YOUR GOD GIVEN RIGHT
TO MAKE AS MUCH MONEY AS YOU CAN
BEFORE YOU DIE.
WE WILL BEAR ARMS WITH OUR WORDS,
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY...
GO TO WAR IF NEED BE, USING ALL TACTICS,
IMAGINABLE... AND UNIMAGINABLE.
BECAUSE WE CREATE EVENTS--
EVENTS TO UNLOCK
SHAREHOLDER VALUE.
AND THAT'S WHY OUR FUND
IS UP 25% YEAR OVER YEAR
FOR THE LAST FIVE YEARS.
WHAT ABOUT ASIA?
WE GOT A GUY
SET UP IN HONG KONG.
REAL SMART. KNOWS HIS STUFF.
[indistinct chatter]
PLAYBOY, YOU'RE TAKING A LONG TIME
TO ROLL THEM DICE, MAN!
Man: COME ON, BABY!
COME ON, BABY! COME ON!
COME ON, MAN, SHIT!
[all yelling]
♪ THROW IT OUT, Y'ALL ♪
♪ THROW, THROW, THROW,
THROW IT OUT, Y'ALL, Y'ALL ♪
♪ THROW IT OUT, Y'ALL,
CASH IN THE CLIP ♪
THROW IT OUT, Y'ALL, Y'ALL ♪
Man: AW!
THAT'S BULLSHIT!
♪ THROW IT OUT, Y'ALL ♪
♪ THROW IT OUT, CASH IN THE CLIP ♪
♪ BIG HOUSE ON THE HILL ♪
♪ GOT THE BIG HOUSE
ON THE HILL ♪
Man: TRADERS ARE ON EDGE
AT THE MOMENT AS THEY AWAIT
FOR THAT FEDERAL RESERVE ANNOUNCEMENT
ON INTEREST RATES.
RAISING RATES SUBSTANTIALLY,
WELL, COULD HAVE A DRAMATIC EFFECT
ON THE U.S. ECONOMY;
IT COULD CHOKE OFF GROWTH,
AS HIGHER BORROWING COSTS
MEAN THAT PEOPLE
FIND IT HARDER TO TAKE OUT LOANS.
EXPERTS ARE WARNING, THOUGH,
THAT THERE IS A NEED
FOR HIGHER BORROWING COSTS
TO CURB INFLATION.
[laughs] ONE PERCENT, RIGHT, CONNER? SURE!
GUESS WORD GOT OUT--YOU REALLY THINK
FED'S GOING TO CUT RATES TO 1%?
THIS IS THE ONE, ANDY.
I CAN FEEL IT.
THAT'S WHAT I LIKE
ABOUT YOU MAN, CRAZY!
YO, CONNER, MAN, THANKS AGAIN
FOR THOSE ANALYTICS YESTERDAY, SPOT ON!
HEY, REMEMBER, BOX SEATS!
SERIOUSLY WITH THIS GUY.
HEY LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
WHAT'S UP? THIS FRIDAY...
YANKEES VERSUS METS?
WHAT YOU GOT, MAN?
JOHNSON VERSUS KISHITA? YES, SIR.
I HEARD WORD ON THE STREET IS
THAT KISHITA BROKE UP WITH HIS FIANCéE,
SO, HE'S GOING TO BE A LITTLE DISTRACTED.
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
COME ON! YANKEES BY TWO.
JUST GO WITH ME ON THIS.
OKAY, THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
[indistinct chatter]
BIG DAY TODAY.
YOU READY?
YEAH.
Woman: MR. BROWN,
YOU ARE CONFERENCE CONNECTED.
Mark: WHAT HAVE YOU GOT FOR ME?
HENDRICKS?
OLD MAN KAFFI OVER AT R.A.W.
IS ABOUT TO KICK THE BUCKET,
SO WE'RE GOING TO SHORT.
OUCH. PRETTY BOY?
WE'RE EXPECTING THE FED
TO ANNOUNCE BIG NUMBERS,
SO WE'RE JUST GOING
TO SIT TIGHT TODAY.
PUSSIES!
OKAY, ONE MORE THING
ON THE AGENDA TODAY, GUYS--
WE'RE GOING TO SAY SAYONARA
TO HONG KONG, EVERYBODY,
IT'S TIME TO DUMP FEI & CHANG.
[sounds of annoyance]
OKAY, EVERYBODY, IF THAT'S IT...
HEY, MARK. IT'S CONNER.
LOOK, BASED ON MY ANALYSIS
OF WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TODAY,
I THINK WE SHOULD ACTUALLY INCREASE
OUR POSITION ON FEI & CHANG.
Mark: TO HOW MUCH?
EIGHTY OR NINETY MILLION.
HAVE YOU COMPLETELY LOST YOUR MIND?
LOOK FED'S IN A BIND,
THEY GOTTA CUT RATES.
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TO DROP THIS 1% BULLSHIT.
I'VE BEEN RE-RUNNING THE NUMBERS, OKAY?
MY GUT IS TELLING ME --YOUR GUT?
YOU THINK THIS IS VEGAS OR SOMETHING
YOU CAN GO AROUND BETTING YOUR GUT?
MARK, I'M SORRY, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO EXCUSE YOUNG MR. CONNER HERE.
IT SEEMS THAT HE HAS JUST AWOKEN
FROM DREAMLAND.
YOU DECREASE RATES, OKAY? CONSUMERS?
THEY'RE GONNA GO OUT,
THEY'RE GONNA RE-FI THEIR HOMES,
THEY'RE GONNA HAVE
A LOT OF CASH.
THEY'RE GONNA HAVE THE CASH
TO BUY THE FLAT SCREEN TVs,
THE PHONES, THE GADGETS,
WHATEVER THEY WANT FOR THEIR KIDS.
AND WHO MAKES
THOSE CONSUMER PRODUCTS? CHINA.
AND WHAT'S THE LARGEST COMPANY
THAT'S GONNA BENEFIT FROM THAT?
I'M SORRY, AM I THE ONLY ONE WHO THINKS
THAT HE IS IN FANTASY LAND RIGHT NOW?
THE FED WILL NEVER CUT RATES TO 1%.
THEY NEVER HAVE,THEY NEVER WILL.
Mark: FIGURE IT OUT AND GET BACK TO ME.
IF YOU WOULD JUST LISTEN TO ME
--NO, YOU LISTEN TO ME!
FEI & CHANG IS DEAD!
THIS MEETING'S OVER,
GET THE FUCK OUT!
YOU THINK YOU'RE SO SMART, DON'T YOU?
YOU AND YOUR MAGIC NUMBERS. OH, GOD.
WELL, LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING, YOU PULL
ANOTHER STUNT IN THERE LIKE THAT AGAIN,
THE ONLY MAGIC YOU'LL BE DOING
IS RUBBING MY MAGIC LAMP.
RUBBING YOUR MAGIC LAMP. GOT IT.
GOOD. ANDY,
DUMP ALL FEI & CHANG AT THE OPEN.
YOU'RE MAKING A MISTAKE.
[laughs] WOW, WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
SOME PUNK COLLEGE DROPOUT
HAS THE PRIVILEGE
OF TELLING ME WHAT TO DO?
I'VE BEEN COVERING YOUR SECTOR
FOR THE LAST SIX MONTHS,
I'VE BEEN DRAFTING YOUR PROPOSALS,
I'VE BEEN CRUNCHING THE NUMBERS,
I'M PRETTY MUCH DOING YOUR JOB.
SO, YEAH, PERSONALLY?
I THINK I DESERVE--
YOU KNOW, I DON'T GIVE A RAT'S ASS
WHAT YOU PERSONALLY THINK.
YOU'RE MAKING UNPRECEDENTED CALLS
IN THE MARKET,
AND YOU'RE DOING
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
THERE'S A CHAIN OF COMMAND HERE,
SO WHEN I SAY GO FUCK YOURSELF,
YOU ASK HOW DEEP.
YOU GOT THAT?
MORRIS, LIGHTEN UP A BIT.
ANDY, IF I WANTED
SOME UNSOLICITED ADVICE
FROM A LITTLE BITCH,
I'LL GO CALL MY EX-WIFE.
LET ME SPELL IT OUT FOR YOU. FED-- 1%.
FEI & CHANG? MASSIVE UPSIDE.
OKAY. OKAY, SMARTASS.
YOU WANNA PUT YOUR MONEY
WHERE YOUR MOUTH IS?
COME ON, WHATEVER.
TEN TO ONE ODDS.
YOU DON'T WANNA BE HERE
AND I DON'T WANT YOU HERE.
SO I TELL YOU WHAT...
EVERYONE, LISTEN UP FOR A SECOND,
LISTEN UP!
I, MORRIS BROWN III,
WILL HEREBY CONTRIBUTE
TO 'SHIT FOR BRAINS'--
THAT'S YOU--
THE SUM OF $50,000,
IF 'SHIT FOR BRAINS' HERE
RUNS AROUND THE OFFICE
WITH HIS PANTS OFF,
SCREAMING "MORRIS IS MY DADDY."
COME ON, CONNER!
I WANNA SEE GRAPE-NUTS! HEY, I'LL DO IT!
CONNER! CONNER! CONNER!
I'LL DO IT WITH YOU, CONNER!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, MAN?
NOTHING IS WORTH
YOUR SELF-RESPECT.
OH, THAT IS SO TOUCHING!
I SWEAR, I JUST DON'T KNOW
WHAT MARK SEES IN YOU.
IF IT WERE UP TO ME, YOU'D BE
NOTHING MORE THAN THE GUY
PICKING THE CORN
OUT OF MY BIG, WET SHIT.
BIG, WET SHIT. GOT IT.
MR. BROWN? MARK IS ON LINE ONE.
THANK YOU.
ANDY? DUMP IT.
Man: STOCKS ARE GETTING
A BOOST AFTER
THE FEDERAL RESERVE REDUCED
THE COST OF BORROWING TO 1%.
THAT'S THE MOVE HERE.
YOU'D HAVE TO GO BACK, WHAT?
TO THE 1940'S TO SEE MONEY THIS CHEAP.
WHAT'S EXPECTED?
RISING HOUSE PRICES.
AS A RESULT, MORE CONSUMER SPENDING.
INVESTORS REALLY AT THE MOMENT
TRYING TO GRAPPLE
WITH THE FED'S MOVE HERE,
TRYING TO MAKE SENSE OF IT.
ONE THING IS FOR CERTAIN, THOUGH--
THIS IS A MAJOR SHIFT
IN MONETARY POLICY,
FOR THE U.S. ECONOMY,
AND WAY, WAY BEYOND THAT.
LETS HAVE A LOOK AT THE MARKETS,
AND THEIR REACTION, IN A BIT MORE DETAIL.
LAURIE?
GET MARK BACK ON THE LINE, WILL YOU?
ENJOY YOUR MEAL.
THANKS.
ONE PERCENT.
WHO COULD HAVE PREDICTED THAT?
NOT A DAMN PERSON.
[door buzzes]
HEY THERE.
HEY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT, MARK?
I CAME TO GIVE YOU THIS.
UH, MINUS FEES, OF COURSE.
WHAT IS THIS? IT'S YOUR EARNINGS
FOR STICKING IT TO MORRIS TODAY.
LOOK, I DIDN'T GET TO BE THE MAN
STANDING BEFORE YOU WITHOUT TAKING A FEW RISKS.
I TOOK THAT BET THAT MORRIS LAID OUT,
AND I TOOK A RISK ON YOU,
AND NOW ITS TIME FOR YOU
TO TAKE A RISK ON YOURSELF.
SAVE THE DAD TALK
FOR YOUR DAUGHTER, OKAY?
YOU EVER BEEN TO HONG KONG?
YOU EVEN BEEN OUT OF THE COUNTRY, KIDDO?
WHAT? YOU GIVING ME
THE SILENT TREATMENT NOW?
I WANT YOU TO GO TO HONG KONG
AND LEAD THE FEI & CHANG TRADE.
THAT'S MORRIS' TRADE.
IT'S YOUR TRADE, NOW.
OH, COME ON, WHY ME?
WHY DON'T YOU GET ONE
OF YOUR PRINCETON,
INBRED SILVERMAN LACKEYS--
OH, DON'T PULL
THE COLLEGE CARD ON ME AGAIN.
YOU DROPPED OUT OF M.I.T.
'CAUSE YOU FELT LIKE IT.
YOU'RE EXTREMELY GIFTED.
YOU HAVE THE EDGE YOUR FATHER HAD.
HE COULD BET AGAINST THE STREET
AND BE RIGHT ABOUT IT.
YOU WANT TO KNOW THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN HIM AND YOU?
SAVE IT. HE WAS A WINNER.
NEVER MADE ANY EXCUSES.
YOU THINK THAT JUST BECAUSE
YOU CAN PREDICT A FEW RIGHT OUTCOMES
THAT THAT MAKES YOU A WINNER?
NO.
YOU'RE NOT A WINNER,
UNTIL YOU DECIDE TO BE ONE.
LOOK, I'M NOT MY FATHER.
YOU WANT TO BET?
GO TO HONG KONG,
BE THE MAN
THAT YOU WERE BORN TO BE.
Conner's Father: CONNER,
I'LL ONLY BE GONE FOR 6 WEEKS.
I'LL CALL YOU WHEN I GET TO HONG KONG.
ONE DAY, YOU'LL UNDERSTAND.
Conner's Mother: CONNER?
IT'S YOUR FATHER...
HE--HE'S...
[horn honks]
HEY, WATCH IT!
[airplane taking off]
FU YIN! WELCOME TO
AMAZING HONG KONG, EVERYBODY!
♪ YEAH, WE EARLY, EARLY, EARLY RISERS ♪
♪ COME TAKE A JOURNEY WITH ME ♪
♪ SOME DAY HOPEFULLY ONE DAY SOON ♪
♪ I CAN FLY PAST THE SKY
AND I TOUCH THE MOON ♪
♪ THEY SAY THE SKY'S THE LIMIT,
BUT I'M LOOKING FAR BEYOND IT ♪
♪ AIMING FOR A COMET,
MAKE A JUMP AND GRAB ON IT ♪
♪ MY HEART BEATING ♪
♪ THE BLOOD OF THE MOTHERLAND
RUNNING THROUGH MY VEINS ♪
♪ LIKE THE SAND THROUGH AN HOURGLASS ♪
♪ LOOK TO THE STARS... ♪
CONNER LEE. HEY, WELCOME TO HONG KONG.
HEY, YOU MUST BE QUENTIN.
AH, DEPENDS ON WHO'S ASKING.
HOW LONG YOU BEEN OUT HERE FOR?
OH, IN THIS PRISON? EIGHT YEARS.
COME ON, I'LL INTRODUCE YOU
TO ALL THE INMATES.
BY THE WAY,HOW WAS THE BUS RIDE?
OH, IT WAS GREAT.GREAT?
[laughs] IT'S LAME AS SHIT.
I JUST WANTED YOU TO GET
ALL THAT TOURISTY CRAP OUT OF THE WAY.
YOU READY TO SEE THE REAL HONG KONG?
YOU BET.
AND HERE WE ARE.
THAT'S RAJ OVER THERE, COVERS INDIA.
HE'S A PUMP AND DUMPER.
JAMES. COVERS MALAYSIA,
THAILAND, DISTRESSED DEBT.
THIS IS YOU. THIS IS ME.
SO, WHAT DO YOU TRADE?
I RUN ALL THE SHORT STRATEGIES.
SO YOU LIKE TO SEE COMPANIES BURN?
WHOA, HEY, COME ON!
SHIT HITS THE FAN THE SAME WAY
IT DOES BACK IN NEW YORK.
HEY, SEXY!
OH, BY THE WAY, CAN YOU PLEASE
ALSO GET ME THAT 7588 FILE?
[laughs]
WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
SLUT. I KNOW IT'S A LOT TO TAKE IN,
BUT DON'T WORRY, I GOT YOUR BACK, BRO.
BY THE WAY, WHERE'D YOU GET THAT SUIT?
LOOKS LIKE 7448 TO ME.
DID YOU SAY MY SUIT LOOKS LIKE SHIT?
Quentin: OUT HERE,
STEALTH WEALTH IS A MUST.
IT'S THE LITTLE THINGS
THAT SEPARATE YOU FROM THE REST.
FIRST IMPRESSIONS? NO, THAT'S BULLSHIT.
YOU ONLY GET ONE CHANCE
TO MAKE ANY KIND OF IMPRESSION.
THAT'S WHY WE WEAR THE BEST...
WE DRINK THE BEST...
WE DRIVE THE BEST...
AND WHEN IT COMES TO CHICKS,
WE ONLY DO THE BEST.
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
WE MUST LEARN
IS THE ART OF GUAN XI.
GUAN XI?
IT'S YOUR BASIC RELATIONSHIPS WITH PEOPLE.
LOOK, BRO, YOU'RE IN HONG KONG NOW.
NOTHING GETS DONE
WITHOUT GIVING GREAT GUAN XI.
WELL, THAT AND ONE OF THESE.
COME MON.
♪ SHOW ME WHAT YOU GOT... ♪
Quentin: CONNER, MEET GARY.
GARY IS NOT ONLY
THE FINANCIAL CONTROLLER AT FEI & CHANG,
HE'S ALSO A HELL OF A SAILOR.
JUST THE MANI WAS TALKING ABOUT.
AH, QUENTIN!
NICE, ACTUALLY
I COULD USE SOME REPORTS--
YOU KNOW WHAT?
TOO MUCH TALKING. LET'S ENJOY!
GUAN XI, HUH?
YEAH.
HERE COMES YOURS NOW, BRO.
WELCOME TO HONG KONG.
NICE TO MEET YOU. I'M--
HEY, GARY.
HEY, CONNER. I GOT WHAT YOU NEED.
GREAT. IF YOU COULD
JUST GIVE ME THE "P AND L"
ON THE SHIPPING DEPARTMENT
AND PUT IT ON A USB DRIVE.
SORRY, IT'S GONNA TAKE A WHILE.
THIS SYSTEM IS IN NEED
OF A COMPLETE UPDATE.
NO PROBLEM.
FATHER, I REALLY DON'T THINK WE SHOULD BE MAKING
THAT DECISION RIGHT NOW.
[sighs] IT'S THE SAAM GWOK.
THE WHAT?
THE THREE KINGDOMS.
DONALD THE CEO, VICTOR HIS OLDER BROTHER,
AND RICHARD THE HEIR APPARENT.
YOU SHOULD GET GOING.
I'LL TAKE THAT.
GARY, WHO IS THIS?
CONNER LEE.
LOOK, I WAS JUST TRYING TO GET
SOME REPORTS HERE FROM GARY.
I WASN'T NOTIFIED OF YOUR VISIT.
WELL, I DIDN'T WANT TO TROUBLE YOU
WITH SUCH TRIVIAL MATTERS, RICHARD.
BUT STANDARD PROCEDURE AT THIS COMPANY
IS FOR ME TO REVIEW ALL REPORTS FIRST.
GARY, NEXT TIME PLEASE INFORM ME
OF ALL SPECIAL GUESTS
BEFORE GIVING OUT PRIVATE INFORMATION.
YES, SIR.
SO WHEN WILL I RECEIVE THE REPORTS?
AT LEAST A MONTH.
A MONTH? I MEAN,
THEY'RE JUST SIMPLE REPORTS.
WHAT YOU MIGHT VIEW AS SIMPLE
MAY BE MORE COMPLEX TO OTHERS.
I CAN SEE THAT.
GLAD YOU'RE CLEAR.
ANITA, I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
MARK DOESN'T LIKE SALT ON HIS EGGS!
SORRY, MA'AM.
A MONTH? WHAT'S THE HOLD UP?
I THOUGHT YOU HAD THIS!
SWEETIE, WHO'S THAT ON THE PHONE?
IT'S CONNER.
HEY, CONNER!
HI, JULIET.
NO. NO GIRLFRIEND.
Mark: LOOK, I DON'T CARE
WHAT THE HOLD UP IS, ALL RIGHT?
WE HAVE A 5% SHARE
IN THE COMPANY, FOR GOD'S SAKE.
WE CAN DO WHATEVER THE--
DADDY, CAN I HAVE A GLASS OF WATER?
YES, HONEY.
Conner: THAT DOESN'T SEEM
TO MEAN ANYTHING TO HIM.
ALL RIGHT. WELL, IT SOUNDS LIKE
HE'S GOT YOU DOWN ON BOTH KNEES...
SO WHILE YOU'RE DOWN THERE,
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE HIM A--
LOOK, I JUST NEED MORE TIME, OKAY?
YEAH, FINE.
KEEP ME POSTED.
HEY, UH, CAN I GET A J.D. STRAIGHT UP?
MAY I?
IT'S A FREE COUNTRY.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I HEAR.
AND WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD?
WELL, IT'S HONG KONG,
IT'S PRACTICALLY CHINA.
THEY CAN CHANGE THE SIDE OF THE ROAD
YOU DRIVE ON JUST LIKE THAT IF THEY WANT TO.
AND WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
THE STATES.
SO YOU DON'T THINK
THE GOVERNMENT CONTROLS YOU THERE?
WE GOT A CONSTITUTION; FREEDOM OF SPEECH.
SO YOU DON'T THINK THE GOVERNMENT
USES MEDIA TO CREATE FEAR AND PANIC
SO YOU'LL STAY IN YOUR LITTLE BOX?
FEAR OF TERRORISM,
NATURAL DISASTERS, ILLNESSES?
I'M SURPRISED YOU'RE ABLE TO SLEEP AT NIGHT.
I'M CONNER. NATALIE WANG.
YOU SEEM TO KNOW
A LOT ABOUT POLITICS.
I STUDIED POLITICAL SCIENCE
AND NOW I JUST--
BUST PEOPLE'S BALLS, HUH?
DO PUBLIC RELATIONS.
AH, SO YOU'RE A PROFESSIONAL
BALL BUSTER?
CAN I GET A GLASS OF RED WINE AND A COKE
OVER TO THAT TABLE OVER THERE? THANKS.
YOU'RE WITH THAT GUY?
NICE TALKING TO YOU, CONNER.
[grunts] LOVE IT! LOVE IT!
GIVE IT TO ME! LOVE THE ENERGY!
COME ON! UPPERCUTS! [grunts]
NICE, ONE MORE! [grunts])
HOW'S THE GUAN XI TODAY, BRO?
[speaking Cantonese]
[grunts]
DUDE, YOUR CHINESE SUCKS.
COME ON, WHAT'S EATING YOU?
WHAT'S THE SCOOP?
THE CEO'S SON.
AH, RICHARD CHANG!
HE'S GOT ALL THE DATA
UNDER LOCK AND KEY.
TYPICAL COCK-SUCKING FAMILY HIERARCHY.
[grunts] ALWAYS GETTING
IN THE WAY OF OUR MONEY.
[grunts] THE PRODIGAL SON,
TRYING TO WEAN HIMSELF
FROM THE FAMILIAL TIT.
ALWAYS TRYING TO PROVE THAT HIS COCK
IS BIGGER THAN HIS DADDY'S.
[grunts]
WHAT DO YOU THINK I SHOULD DO?
HOW MUCH MONEY YOU GOT?
EH? [chuckles]
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IT'S PRETTY NICE.
OKAY. WE'RE TALKING HIGH-LEVEL QUAN XI.
RICHARD ALREADY HAS MONEY AND POWER,
BUT YOU CAN'T BUY HIM OUT.
THE ONLY THING YOU CAN TAKE
FROM HIM IS HIS RESPECT.
DO THAT, AND HE MAY JUST GIVE YOU
THE KEYS TO THE FEI & CHANG CASTLE.
[Quentin] LET'S GET YOU UP TO SPEED BECAUSE TONIGHT,
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE GOING MANO Y MANO.
THE GAME DU JOUR IS BACCARAT.
IT'S SIMPLE. YOU CAN BET
EITHER BANKER OR PLAYER.
EACH SIDE GETS TWO CARDS.
ADD THEM UP, DROP THE FIRST DIGIT,
AND THAT'S A POINT.
CLOSEST TO NINE WINS.
IF YOU CAME HERE FOR ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THE COMPANY--
NO, I JUST CAME TO PLAY SOME CARDS.
FINE.
FUN GAME.
GOD, YOU'RE SO AMERICAN.
I AM AMERICAN.
AND YOU WANT EVERYTHING RIGHT AWAY
AND YOU THINK YOU'RE ALWAYS RIGHT,
THAT YOU ARE ENTITLED
TO WHATEVER YOU WANT
AND YOU CAN TAKE AS YOU PLEASE,
WITH NO PATIENCE,
NO CONSEQUENCE.
YOU'RE THE BLIND LEADING THE BLIND.
NO TIES TO FAMILY,
OR OF HERITAGE NOR TRADITION.
YOU THINK YOU KNOW EVERYTHING,
WHEN YOU HAVE
NO UNDERSTANDING OF ANYTHING.
[men chanting]
YEAH!
[applause]
WANT TO GO AGAIN?
YOU BET.
[woman giggles]
[sighs]
[door opens]
[laughing]
WHOA. WINNER WINNER,
DIM SUM DINNER.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
GO WAIT OUTSIDE. COME ON.
WHAT HAPPENED?
I JUST LOST A HUNDRED THOUSAND. OW.
EVERY TIME I BET, HE JUST BETS
AGAINST ME AND WINS.
RELAX. YOU CAN DO THIS, BRO.
YOU EVER PLAY BOTH SIDES BEFORE?
WHAT?
LOOK, FIRST YOU BET
BOTH PLAYER AND BANKER.
FORCE HIM TO DECIDE.
AFTER HE'S CHOSEN,
YOU BET THE REST
OF WHAT YOU HAVE AGAINST HIM.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WHAT ABOUT THE TREND?
FUCK THE TREND. PLAY WHAT YOU HAVE
IN FRONT OF YOU.
SHAKE IT UP. LIVE A LITTLE.
YOU REALLY SHOULD
JUST GIVE UP NOW.
AND SPOIL ALL THE FUN?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
BEING AMERICAN.
WELL, PLEASE, BY ALL MEANS,
KEEP PUMPING YOUR AMERICAN DOLLARS
INTO OUR ECONOMY.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
WE LET YOUR KIND IN HERE.
HOW ABOUT WE MAKE THIS INTERESTING?
I WIN; YOU GIVE ME THE NUMBERS
I NEED TO DO MY JOB.
I LOSE...YOU LOSE...
WHAT COULD YOU POSSIBLY HAVE
THAT I DON'T ALREADY OWN?
I LOSE;
ME AND MY AMERICAN DOLLARS GO HOME.
DEAL.
PLAYER WINS.
[sighs]
NO HARD FEELINGS.
YOUR INTENTIONS BETTER BE
AS GOOD AS YOUR LUCK.
YEAH. NO, HE'S DOING GOOD.
HE'S DOING REALLY GOOD.
OH, HEY I GOTTA GO.
DID IT WORK?
YEAH, BRO.
REALLY?
YES, REALLY.
[laughs] DAMN!
I GUESS WE GOT
SOMETHING TO CELEBRATE.
[laughs]
[dialing]
[ringing]
WHAT DO YOU HAVE FOR ME?
Conner: ALL RIGHT.
SO, RETAIL OUTLETS SEEM FINE.
SOME FACTORIES ARE LOSING MONEY,
BUT IT SEEMS
THE IMPORT/EXPORT BUSINESS
HAS SOME SERIOUS CASH FLOW ISSUES,
AND THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO TARGET.
RIGHT NOW, THEY'VE BEEN WORKING WITH
SILVERMAN INVESTMENT BANKERS
TO COVER THEIR DEBT.
DONALD HAS BEEN RELUCTANT
TO TAKE ON THIS RISK.
THIS TYPE OF INDECISIVENESS
HAS SHAREHOLDERS FED UP,
KEEPING THE STOCK PRICE DOWN.
IT'S A FAMILY-RUN COMPANY
WITH YOUNGER BROTHER DONALD
SWIFTLY LOSING CONTROL.
NOW, THE COMPANY
HAS BEEN CAPITALIZING
ON ALL THE GROWTH OF THE U.S.,
BUT THEY'VE BEEN HELD BACK
BECAUSE MANAGEMENT
CAN'T SEEM TO KEEP COSTS DOWN.
WITH THE SPECIFIC CHANGES
I'VE GOT LINED UP,
I'D SAY THE STOCK
COULD JUMP AT LEAST 20 TO 30%.
THIRTY PERCENT, SOUNDS GOOD.
KEEP ME POSTED. GOTTA GO.
RIGHT.
[beeps]
[rings]
CONNER!HEY!
EVERYONE'S BETTING
YOU'D BE SENT HOME BY NOW.
WELL, INCREASE MY POSITION
ON FEI & CHANG
TO 200 MILLION.
TWO HUNDRED BUCKS
ON FEI & CHANG?
THOUGHT YOU'RE ONLY AUTHORIZED
TO DO A HUNDRED.
BOTTOM OF THE NINTH, BUDDY.
TIME TO CALL MY SHOT.
OKAY, YOU'RE THE BOSS.
[woman speaking Cantonese]
THANK YOU.
THEY SHOULDN'T BE MUCH LONGER.
CAN I OFFER YOU A COFFEE?
NO, THANKS.
[video game noises
HEY, KID.
WHAT?
WANT TO KNOW A SECRET?
OKAY.
[whispering] They're trying
to kill me with coffee.
REALLY?
Yeah.
See, if I hadn't drank
so much coffee
when I was younger,
I'd be a giant.
COOL!
I'D BE A GIANT! [roars]
I'M GOING TO EAT YOU UP AND--
MR. LEE?
UH...
WE'RE READY FOR YOU NOW.
RIGHT.
BYE, NATALIE.
OH, I'LL SEE YOU!
OKAY, SEE YOU TOMORROW.
OKAY, BYE!
COME ON, LETS GO.
SO IN SUMMARY,
I RECOMMEND YOU, ONE:
CLOSE DOWN THESE NINE FACTORIES.
TWO: TERMINATE SEVERAL
POOR-PERFORMING MANAGERS,
LISTED IN APPENDIX B.
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY, THREE:
SELL OFF THE IMPORT/EXPORT BUSINESS
FOR ITS NEGATIVE CASH FLOW.
MR. LEE.
THE LIST OF THE MANAGERS HERE,
I WILL NOT FIRE ANY OF THEM.
AND THESE WORKERS IN THE FACTORIES
THAT YOU WANT US TO CLOSE DOWN?
THEY HAVE FAMILIES,
SONS AND DAUGHTERS TO SUPPORT.
NOT ONLY THAT,
THEY ARE ALL PART OF MY BIG FAMILY.
I THINK YOU'RE MISSING
THE POINT HERE.
SEE, THE FACTORIES,
THEY'RE INEFFICIENT AND BLOATED.
IN ANY EVENT, I'M MORE CONCERNED
ABOUT THE IMPORT/EXPORT BUSINESS.
DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THE IMPORT/EXPORT BUSINESS?
THERE ARE HIGHS AND LOWS.
RIGHT NOW HAPPENS TO BE A LOW.
FOR THE LAST THREE YEARS?
YOU ARE ASKING ME TO ELIMINATE
AN INTEGRAL PART OF MY COMPANY--
THAT COULD EVENTUALLY BRING DOWN
THE REST OF THE COMPANY.
FATHER, YOU CAN'T SERIOUSLY ALLOW THIS GUY
TO MANHANDLE THE FATE OF THE COMPANY.
THE FACT THAT YOU'RE EVEN CONSIDERING--
RICHARD...
I THINK I SPEAK FOR THE BOARD.
YOU KNOW WHAT? ACTUALLY,
I'D LIKE TO HEAR FROM THE BOARD THEMSELVES.
YOUR PLAN WILL SIMPLY NOT WORK.
LOOK, I'VE RUN THE NUMBERS
AND RESPECTFULLY MAKE
THE CHANGES OR SOMEONE ELSE WILL.
SOMEONE ELSE?
ARE YOU THREATENING ME, MR. LEE?
IT'S NOT A THREAT, IT'S A PLAIN FACT.
LOOK, YOU THINK
THAT JUST BECAUSE YOUR FATHER
GAVE YOU THE COMPANY A LONG TIME AGO
YOU CAN JUST SWEEP THIS
UNDER THE RUG?
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT FAMILY, MR. LEE?
ENOUGH TO SEE THAT IT'S
SKEWING YOUR JUDGEMENT.
I DON'T LIKE YOUR TONE! [inaudible whisper]
GOOD DAY, MR. LEE!
I'M NOT FINISHED.
I THINK YOU ARE, MR. LEE.
FATHER, JUST LISTEN TO WHAT I HAVE TO SAY
FOR ONCE, WITHOUT BEING SO THICK-HEADED.
ENOUGH! PLEASE, EVERYBODY OUT!
RICHARD! RICHARD! RICHARD!
NOW, YOU MUST LEARN
WHICH BATTLE TO FIGHT.
[speaking Cantonese]
HE NEVER LISTENS.
COMES FROM YOUR GRANDMOTHER.
I JUST WANT HIM TO KNOW
THAT THERE'S ANOTHER WAY.
RICHARD, I WANT TO KNOW...
[speaking Cantonese]
...OR SOME NEW TECHNOLOGY
WHICH I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
ALL I WANT TO KNOW IS, HOW IS IT COMING?
ALMOST FINISHED.
IT'S GOING TO REVOLUTIONIZE THE INDUSTRY,
AND HE WON'T EVEN LISTEN.
[speaking Cantonese]
EVERY NIGHT.
GREAT.
PERFECT IT. MAKE IT WORK.
[speaking Cantonese]
THIS TIME I'M GONNA MAKE HIM LISTEN.
ALL FOR THE FAMILY, RIGHT?
FOR THE FAMILY.
[phone rings]
KEEP ME INFORMED. OKAY?
[speaking Cantonese]
Conner: YEAH, I THOUGHT THEY'D AGREE
TO SOME OF THE CHANGES.
WELL, I'M SURE YOU'LL FIGURE
SOMETHING OUT.
REALLY? I MEAN...
I JUST DON'T KNOW
IF I'M CUT OUT FOR THIS.
LOOK, YOU ARE DOING EXACTLY
WHAT YOU SHOULD BE DOING.
THANKS.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES YOU PUSH
WHEN REALLY WHAT YOU NEED TO DO IS PULL.
AND GOING IN FROM THE FRONT DOOR
HASN'T BEEN WORKING.
MAYBE THERE'S A SIDE DOOR?
YEAH, KEEP GOING.
WELL, DONALD'S GOT A LOT
OF LEGACIES TO MAINTAIN,
AND HALF HIS FAMILY
PRACTICALLY RUNS THE JOINT.
WHY DON'T WE GET SOMEBODY
FROM THE OUTSIDE TO INVESTIGATE?
SHAKE IT UP A LITTLE.
YEAH, SHAKE IT UP A LITTLE.
I LIKE THE WAY YOU'RE THINKING.
KEEP GOING.
[beeps]
[sighs]
CAN YOU BELIEVE
THIS GUY'S SHIRT, HUH?
[speaking Cantonese]
Conner: DEAR MR. JANG,
VICE PRESIDENT OF OPERATIONS.
WE HAVE ATTAINED MATERIALS
OF YOUR POTENTIAL INVOLVEMENT
IN ILLEGAL ACTIVITIES REGARDING
FEI & CHANG ENTERPRISES.
MANY KEY EMPLOYEES
HAVE ALREADY TESTIFIED,
AND WE ARE FORCED
TO TAKE IMMEDIATE ACTION.
WE'VE THUS NOTIFIED
THE INDEPENDENT COMMISSION AGAINST CORRUPTION.
LORRAINE IP.
IN RECOGNITION OF YOUR CONTRIBUTION
TO THE COMPANY THUS FAR,
WE ARE OFFERING YOU THE OPTION
TO RESIGN FROM YOUR POST,
ELSE, PROSECUTION BY THE COMPANY
AND THE HONG KONG GOVERNMENT
SHALL BE HELD
TO THE FULLEST EXTENT WITHOUT LENIENCY.
I'M IN CORPORATE SALES--
YOU KNOW, TAKE CLIENTS OUT,
MAKE SURE THEY'RE ENTERTAINED.
I SEE.
RESPECTFULLY YOURS,
AN INDEPENDENT THIRD PARTY
ACTING ON BEHALF OF THE COMPANY FEI & CHANG
AND ITS SHAREHOLDERS.
[door opens and closes]
[speaking Cantonese]
YOU'RE A DISGRACE
TO YOUR FATHER'S MEMORY.
[speaking Cantonese]
♪ MONEY AND THE POWER,
MONEY AND THE POWER ♪
I REALLY DIDN'T THINK
YOU HAD IT IN YOU.
YOU HAVE GOT THOSE FEI & CHANG PANSIES
RUNNING AROUND WITH THEIR PANTIES
AROUND THEIR ANKLES!
[all laugh]
HEY, YOU SEE THAT DUDE OVER THERE? YEAH.
THAT'S MY BUDDY "DIU LE LO MO."
HE'S THE MAN AROUND HERE,
REALLY FRIENDLY GUY.
GO INTRODUCE YOURSELF.
OKAY.
HEY! DIU LE LO MO!
HEY? DIU LE LO MO!
HUH?
[speaking Cantonese]
WHOA! HEY... YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU SIT
YOUR PUNK ASS DOWN?
[scoffs]
[speaking Cantonese]
[laughs]
WHAT THE FUCK, DUDE?
CHINESE LESSONS!
WHAT'D I SAY?
"GO FUCK YOUR MOM."
All: OOH!
BUT HEY, SPEAKING OF MOTHERS...
HOLD THAT THOUGHT,
WE GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
All: HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
WHA--
HOW'D YOU GUYS...?
I'M THE KING OF INTEL, BRO.
MAKE A WISH.
[blows]
All: CHEERS!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO ME.
James: OH, YEAH, YOU WISH!
WHATEVER, MAN,YOU LIKE BOYS!
GO BACK HIM UP, JAMES.
HEY, I THINK WE STARTED OFF
ON THE WRONG FOOT.
DO I KNOW YOU?
WELL, THAT DEPENDS...
LOOK, IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
DO YOU MIND JOINING US
FOR A DRINK?
I DON'T DRINK
WITH NEANDERTHAL BANKERS.
LOOK, I THINK YOU HAVE ME MISTAKEN
FOR SOMEBODY ELSE.
LET'S SEE. YOU'RE A TRADER,
SUPERCAPITALIST INC.,
TRYING TO DISSOLVE A COMPANY
SO HE CAN GAIN MONETARY REWARDS
IN THE SHORT TERM
WHILE DESTROYING LIVES
IN THE LONG TERM.
[blows] DOES THAT ABOUT SUM IT UP?
WOW, THAT GUY SOUNDS
LIKE A REAL ASSHOLE.
NO, I'M A FARMER.
A FARMER?
YEAH, I HAVE A LITTLE PLOT
OF LAND IN CHINA,
GROW CORN,CONVERT IT TO BIOFUEL,
HELP MAKE THE WORLD
A BETTER PLACE.
CONNER? CUT THE CRAP.
SO YOU DO REMEMBER ME?
YEAH, I REMEMBER YOU MAKING A COMPLETE ASSHOLE
OF YOURSELF IN THE BOARDROOM.
HEY, I'M JUST TRYING TO MAKE PEACE HERE.
MAKE PEACE? YOU MAKE PEACE?
NO, MORE LIKE YOU WANT A PIECE.
I KNOW GUYS LIKE YOU.
YOU THINK YOU'RE ALL ENTITLED.
GROW UP IN A RICH FAMILY,
GO TO AN IVY LEAGUE SCHOOL...
YOU SHOW UP IN ASIA, THINKING
THE WORLD IS YOUR PLAYGROUND.
...BEHIND YOUR EARS,
TAKE SOME OF THAT HAIR--
COME ON, LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
SAVED BY THE SLAP.
[chuckles] FUNNY.
LOOK, IF YOU'RE REALLY SERIOUS
ABOUT MAKING A DIFFERENCE,
HERE'S MY CARD.
OH HO HO HO! DO I HAVE
A GOOD ONE FOR YOU TODAY!
FEI & CHANG ENTERPRISES!
SELL YOUR BABIES, SELL YOUR CHILDREN,
SELL YOUR GIRLFRIEND! YOUR LIFE IS OVER!
FEI & CHANG? MORE LIKE FEI & BANG
'CAUSE YOU'RE [bleep]!
♪ WE READY, SET, GET GO ♪
♪ WE JUST MET, GET LOW ♪
♪ TEXT IT ON MY CELL PHONE ♪
♪ GOT MY GIRLS TO PARTY, HELLO ♪
♪ WE OUT LIKE IT'S OUR LAST NIGHT ♪
♪ WE HIGH LIKE IT'S A SPACE FLIGHT ♪
♪ POP BOTTLES SO WE DO IT RIGHT ♪
♪ GOES UNTIL THE MORNING LIGHT ♪
♪ FEELING LIKE A MILLION... ♪
THE BIG FINANCIAL NEWS
OF COURSE IS FEI & CHANG
AND THE FUTURE OF ITS CEO
DONALD CHANG.
[speaking Cantonese]
I'VE LOST MONEY FIVE YEARS
IN A ROW, SO ABSOLUTELY.
[speaking Cantonese]
[engine revs]
♪ EVERYTHING'S FOR ME ♪
♪ MY SWAGGER'S ALWAYS ON ♪
♪ THIS IS MY CITY ♪
♪ IT'S MY CITY ♪
♪ TONIGHT WE'RE GONNA GET
OURSELVES DRUNK ♪
♪ DANCE TILL THE MORNING LIGHT... ♪
Michael: IT'S CALLED A POISON PILL.
ESSENTIALLY WE'RE DILUTING THE NUMBER
OF SHARES CURRENTLY ON THE MARKET.
WHEN WE INCREASE THE NUMBER OF SHARES,
THE STOCK PRICE GOES DOWN.
SO BASICALLY WHAT YOU'RE SAYING IS,
I SHOULD INCREASE
THE NUMBER OF SHARES AVAILABLE
IN ORDER TO HURT
THE SHARE PRICE?
EXACTLY! AND WHEN
THE STOCK PRICE GOES DOWN--
HE LOSES MONEY.
HELL, EVERYBODY LOSES MONEY,
AT LEAST IN THE SHORT TERM.
LOOK, I KNOW THESE HEDGE FUND GUYS.
AS SOON AS THE STOCK PRICE
GOES DOWN, HE'LL LIQUIDATE.
AND IF I DO THIS, WHAT ARE MY RISKS?
RISK? YOUR LEADERSHIP
WOULD BE HIGHLY QUESTIONED!
YOU WILL LOSE THE CONTROL
OF EVERYTHING!
RICHARD, THIS IS NOT THE TIME!
IF NOT, WHEN?
FATHER, PLEASE. I HAVE AN IDEA.
MR. CHAU AND I HAVE BEEN WORKING
ON THIS PROGRAM--
RICHARD, WE NEED RESULTS,
NOT YOUR CRAZY IDEAS.
THEY'RE NOT CRAZY! WHAT'S CRAZY IS
THAT YOU ARE TALKING TO THIS GUY!
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
RICHARD, I'M NOT GOING TO LISTEN.
YOU ARE EMBARRASSING ME. JUST GO.
COME ON, MAKE HIM LISTEN! RICHARD...
SORRY, MR. BAKER.
AH, FAMILY, WHAT YOU GONNA DO?
FACT OF THE MATTER IS,
YOU STILL HAVE TO PAY DOWN
THOSE DEBTS WE DISCUSSED.
THIS JUST GIVES YOU ALL
THE MORE REASON TO DO SO NOW.
I UNDERSTAND.
SO WHERE DID IT ALL GO WRONG?
[sighs] SEEMS LIKE FROM THE START.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
[speaking Cantonese]
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I UNDERSTAND. IT'S ALL RIGHT.
[speaking Cantonese]
WHAT THEN?
YOU'LL TAKE OVER FOR ME?
[speaking Cantonese]
AND I AM SURE FATHER
IS VERY PROUD OF YOU.
[lights cigar]
[speaking Cantonese]
HE HAS SO MUCH CONTEMPT FOR ME.
I CAN'T EVEN RELATE TO HIM.
[speaking Cantonese]
YOU DON'T EVER HAVE
TO APOLOGIZE TO ME.
FUCKING BRILLIANT!
THEY'RE ON THE RUN.
Conner: GOT THE MARKETS IN A FRENZY.
STOCK'S UP 10%. I'M GONNA TAKE THE GAIN.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
DON'T SELL, DON'T SELL.
KEEP THE PRESSURE ON. THIS IS GOOD.
YEAH, WHAT I TELL YOU ABOUT TAKING RISKS?
I NEED A BIG TRADE OUT THERE
TO SHOW THESE INVESTORS,
AND THIS IS THE ONE.
ALL RIGHT, I GOTTA GO, CHAMP.
OKAY.
[beeps]
YEAH, IT'S ME.
NOW LOOK, YOU SAID THIS WAS GUARANTEED.
I HAVE THE ENTIRE FUND
RIDING ON THIS TRADE.
IF I GO DOWN, YOU GO DOWN.
GET IT DONE.
HEY, THANKS FOR MEETING ME.
SO WHAT DO YOU WANT, CONNER?
WELL, WITH ALL THE PRESS
THAT'S BEEN GOING ON,
I JUST THOUGHT WE SHOULD TALK.
TALK? YOU WANT ME TO TELL YOU
EVERYTHING I KNOW
AND THEN AFTER HAVE A DRINK
OR TWO UP IN YOUR HOTEL ROOM?
YEAH, I'M SORRY, NATALIE. I WISH WE MET
UNDER DIFFERENT CIRCUMSTANCES.
DIFFERENT CIRCUMSTANCES
WOULDN'T HAVE CHANGED ANYTHING.
SO YOU GOT ME ALL FIGURED OUT, HUH?
YOU ASSUME I'M THIS MONSTER.
YOU THINK ANY OTHER FUND'S GONNA
TREAT YOU ANY DIFFERENTLY?
IF IT'S NOT ME,
IT'S GONNA BE SOMEBODY ELSE.
THAT IS SO IRRESPONSIBLE.
AND THAT'S THE THING THAT GOT US
INTO THIS MESS IN THE FIRST PLACE.
FOR SOMEONE THAT ACTS LIKE
YOU KNOW EVERYTHING, THAT IS YOUR BEST ANSWER?
LOOK, I TRIED, NATALIE, OKAY?
AND I'M THE GUY JUST TRYING
TO MAKE A PAYCHECK.
AT WHAT COST?
ACTIONS HAVE CONSEQUENCES, CONNER.
I'D AT LEAST RESPECT YOU
IF YOU OWN UP TO YOUR OWN CHOICES.
I'M JUST TRYINGTO DO THE BEST I CAN
IN THE BEST WAY I KNOW HOW.
YEAH, I'M SURE.
CONVINCE ME. CHALLENGE ME.
COME ONE, MAKE ME UNDERSTAND FOR ONCE.
DON'T JUST WRITE ME OFF
LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE.
WELL, HOW DO I KNOW I CAN TRUST YOU?
HOW DO I KNOW THAT ANYTHING I SHOW YOU
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO USE AGAINST ME?
WELL, FIRST OF ALL...
YES, I DID GO TO AN IVY LEAGUE COLLEGE.
WHEN I WAS WORKING WITH A PROFESSOR,
I HAPPENED TO PROVE HIM WRONG.
SO HE FLUNKED ME.
LOOK, I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE WHEN SOMEONE DOESN'T BELIEVE IN YOU.
IF YOU'VE GOT A SOLUTION THAT MAKES SENSE, I'LL LISTEN.
THERE IS ANOTHER WAY.
BUT IF I LET YOU IN ON IT,
IT'S GONNA CHALLENGE YOUR VIEWS,
AND THEN YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO MAKE A DECISION.
I CALLED YOU, REMEMBER?
LOOK, IF YOU GOT SOMETHING
THAT MAKES SENSE,
I'LL BE THE FIRST TO SPEAK UP.
OKAY, I'LL SET UP AN APPOINTMENT.
GREAT.
WE SHOULD REALLY ORDER.
YEAH, GREAT.
I DON'T...
YES, I KNOW. I FORGOT. YEAH.
USELESS.
GIZZARDS, LUNG, INTESTINE.
CLOTTED BLOOD.
ALL RIGHT, YOU ORDER.
[speaking Cantonese]
[Natalie laughs]
SO, UH, THANKS FOR SHOWING ME THAT SPOT.
FOOD WAS DELICIOUS.
WELL, THERE'S MORE TO HONG KONG
THAN WHAT YOUR PALS SHOW YOU.
MAYBE I NEED A NEW PAL.
NICE TRY, CONNER.
NO, I THINK AS WORKING COLLEAGUES,
IT'S GOOD WE ESTABLISH--
WAIT, HOLD ON, HOLD ON.
THIS IS A FIRST DATE, RIGHT?
WE'RE NOT WORKING COLLEAGUES.
DON'T PUSH YOUR LUCK, CONNER.
WELL, I'M GLAD WE FINALLY MADE PEACE.
OR SO YOU THINK.
NO, WE'VE ONLY JUST BEGUN, CONNER.
WELL, THIS IS ME.
THANKS FOR WALKING ME HOME.
MY PLEASURE.
YOU REALLY DIDN'T HAVE TO,
BUT THANK YOU.
I WANTED TO.
GOODNIGHT, CONNER.
GOODNIGHT.
HEY, THINK ABOUT WHAT I SAID, OKAY?
I WILL. I PROMISE.
[speaking Cantonese]
HEY, YOU ALL RIGHT?
[speaking Cantonese] WHAT?
YOU SHOULD GO BACK
TO WHERE YOU CAME FROM.
[speaking Cantonese]
[hits wall]
AH, MR. LEE. THANK YOU
FOR COMING TO SEE ME.
LET'S JUST GET THIS OVER WITH.
I TAKE IT YOU'VE DECIDED
TO MAKE THE CHANGES?
YOU KNOW, YOU NEARLY HAD ME CONVINCED.
AND THEN I REALIZED SOMETHING.
AND IT ALL BECAME VERY CLEAR TO ME.
HOW WELL DO YOU KNOW MY COMPANY?
INHERITED THE COMPANY
FROM YOUR FATHER,
MADE ACQUISITIONS IN THE '80s,
WENT PUBLIC IN 1992.
YES.
AND I BET YOU CAN TELL ME HOW MANY WORKERS
I HAVE,HOW MANY FACTORIES I HAVE,
WHAT MY TOTAL REVENUE WAS LAST YEAR.
25,320 WORKERS, 30 FACTORIES,1.7 BILLION.
AND YOU THINK YOU KNOW MY COMPANY
BECAUSE YOU READ A REPORT.
MR. LEE, LOOK OUT THERE.
THOUSANDS OF CONTAINERS.
BEYOND THE CONTAINERS
ARE THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE.
IT TOOK ME A LONG TIME TO LEARN
THAT IT'S THE PEOPLE THAT MATTERS,
IT'S THE PEOPLE THAT MAKES A BUSINESS A SUCCESS,
NOT IDEAS.
IT'S THE PEOPLE WE SHOULD CARE ABOUT.
WITH THE AMOUNT OF SHARES YOU NOW HAVE
COMES THE POWER TO WIELD
THAT MIGHTY SWORD.
THAT SWORD CAN UNITE
OR DESTROY MY COMPANY.
MR. LEE, I JUST WANT TO REMIND YOU...
THE CHOICE IS YOURS.
HEY.
THANKS FOR COMING.
A PROMISE IS A PROMISE.
Natalie: UNCLE? WE'RE HERE!
HI, NATALIE! HI!
HOW ARE YOU?
AH, THIS MUST BE THE INFAMOUS MR. LEE.
GOOD TO MEET YOU.
CONNER, THIS IS MR. CHAU, V.P. OF TECH.
WELCOME, WELCOME.
AND I THINK YOU'VE ALREADY MET KELVIN.
[roars]
LETS SHOW HIM
WHAT WE'VE BEEN WORKING ON.
OKAY, LET GET THINGS SET UP.
COME ON, HAVE A SEAT.
HELLO, LITTLE MAN.
[speaking Cantonese]
SO, UH, WHAT KIND OF GAME
YOU GOT THERE?
OH! IT'S AN ONLINE GAME. IT'S REALLY FUN.
SEE, YOU CAN BUY COMPANIES
AND SELL COMPANIES.
AND YOU CAN USE THOSE MONEY
THAT YOU EARN TO BUY OTHER COOL STUFF.
LIKE BOATS, CARS, AND HOUSES.
THE MORE MONEY I EARN,
THE HIGHER MY STATUS.
WELL, I GOT A GAME FOR YOU.
YEAH?
READY? ROCK, PAPER... SCISSORS!
[chuckles] YOU KNOW THIS GAME.
ALL RIGHT. YEAH.
Both: ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS!
ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS!
YES, GOT YOU! OH!
OKAY, I'M ALL SET.
HERE, HAVE A SEAT.
ALL RIGHT.SEE...
RICHARD AND NATALIE AND I'VE BEEN WORKING
FOR THE PAST FEW MONTHS
ON THIS NEW SUPPLY CHAIN
MANAGEMENT SYSTEM.
YOU KNOW, I MODELED THE WHOLE SYSTEM
AFTER KELVIN'S GAME OVER THERE.
SO GIVE EACH EMPLOYEE
MORE INCENTIVE TO BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THEIR OWN SHIPMENTS AND CONTAINERS...
IN A FUN AND EASY FORMAT.
WHY HAVEN'T YOU GUYS
TOLD ANYBODY ABOUT THIS?
WELL, IT WAS RICHARD'S IDEA,
BUT DONALD HASN'T REALLY LISTENED
TO RICHARD FOR A WHILE NOW.
DAD, CAN MR. LEE STAY FOR DINNER?
AH, YOU READ MY MIND!
OH, WE COULDN'T POSSIBLY--
WE'D LOVE TO.
[no audio]
HI.
HEY.
THIS IS NICE.
YOU'RE REALLY DOING IT RIGHT.
WELL, IT TOOK ME A LONG TIME TO GET IT.
WORKING ALL THE TIME...
FOR WHAT? FOR MONEY?
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
ONE COULD ASK FOR IN THIS LIFETIME?
AM I INTERRUPTING ANYTHING?
OF COURSE NOT.
UM, IN FACT, I NEED TO GET IN
AND GET SOMETHING CHECKED ON.
[both chuckle]
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU MIND ME ASKING,
BUT WHAT WERE YOUR PARENTS LIKE?
DAD DIED WHEN I WAS EIGHT.
MOM TOOK CARE OF ME
THE BEST THAT SHE COULD.
MY DAD WAS A TRADER
ON THE NEW YORK STOCK EXCHANGE.
USED TO SPEND A LOT OF TIME HERE, THOUGH.
ONE DAY, HE JUST NEVER CAME BACK.
HOW ABOUT YOUR MOM?
SHE HATED THE STATES.
WHEN I TURNED 18, SHE JUST MOVED AWAY.
HAVEN'T SEEN HER SINCE.
DO YOU MISS HER?
YOU SHOULD TAKE THE TIME TO GET TO KNOW
YOUR MOM BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN REALLY HARD
FOR YOU TO COME BACK HERE.
AND AFTER ALL THIS,
YOU STILL DECIDED TO BECAME A TRADER.
HE USED TO LOVE TO GAMBLE.
HE USED TO GAMBLE
AT THIS LOCAL MAHJONG PARLOR IN CHINATOWN.
HE USED TO SAY,
[deep voice] "IF YOU AREN'T GAMBLING,
YOU AREN'T LIVING."
[both chuckle]
[deep voice]JUST LIKE THAT?
[deep voice] YES.
[both laugh]
THAT'S ALL I HAVE LEFT OF HIM.
IT'S A WORN OUT PIECE OF PLASTIC...
BUT IT GIVES ME PEACE.
I THINK THIS IS WHAT HE
WOULD'VE WANTED, YOU KNOW.
AND WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I DON'T KNOW ANYMORE.
UNCLE CONNER! READ ME A BEDTIME STORY!
[both chuckle]
HI, KELVIN.
HI. HI.
SAVED BY THE SLAP.
[chuckles] RIGHT.
LITTLE MAN, I'M GONNA HAVE TO TEACH YOU
A LITTLE THING CALLED TIMING.
[no audio]
[screams]
Andy: CONNER. WHAT'S UP, BRO?
BRO? SINCE WHEN DID YOU USE "BRO"?
WHAT'S UP, ANDY?
LISTEN, MAN,
I WAS FILLING ORDERS THE OTHER DAY
WHEN I NOTICED SOME SHORT POSITIONS
OUT OF NOWHERE ON YOUR TRADE.
WHO RUNS THE SHORTS OUT THERE?
QUENTIN. BUT HE WOULDN'T--
THEY'RE ALL COMING FROM AN ASIA TRADING DESK
THROUGH AN OFFSHORE ACCOUNT.
YOU HAVE ANY PROOF?
I CAN'T BE SURE. I MEAN...
I'D HAVE TO RUN OUR IN-HOUSE RECORDS
WITH THE RECORDS FROM FEI & CHANG.
FEI & CHANG? YOU KNOW HOW HARD IT IS
TO GET ANY INFORMATION OUT OF FEI & CHANG?
CONNER, THIS IS LARGE.
LOOK, MAN, WHEN I ADD UP
ALL THE SHORTS,
THE POSITION IS A BILLION U.S.
OUR POSITION IS 200 MILLION.
ALL I'M SAYING IS THAT SOMETHING
IS DEFINITELY GOING DOWN OUT THERE,
AND THE STOCK PRICE IS A LIKELY CANDIDATE.
JUST WATCH YOUR BACK.
[beeps]
HEY.
CONNER, HEY, HOW ARE YOU?
THIS IS MICHAEL.
HEY, CONNER.
HEY, UH, I DIDN'T KNOW
THIS WAS A GROUP LUNCH.
COME ON, HAVE A SEAT, BRO .
SO HOW DO YOU TWO KNOW EACH OTHER?
OH, MICHAEL AND I WENT TO PENN TOGETHER.
SO YOU'VE KNOWN EACH OTHER
FOR A LONG TIME?
THAT RIGHT. FELL OUT OF TOUCH A WHILE BACK,
BUT JUST BUMPED INTO EACH OTHER AGAIN.
I GUESS EVERYBODY'S MOVING OUT HERE NOW.
YEAH, I GUESS SO.
HI, MR. BAKER.WHAT CAN I GET FOR YOU TODAY?
JUST THE USUAL, SWEETIE.OKAY.
YEAH, I'VE BEEN COMING HERE
FOR A WHILE NOW.
MUST BE NICE TO BE IN THE KNOW.
IT IS. IT WASN'T
ALWAYS LIKE THIS, THOUGH.
FIRST TIME I CAME IN HERE,
THIS PLACE WAS A COMPLETE SHITHOLE.
NO ENGLISH ON THE MENU FOR WESTERNERS,
YOU KNOW THE DRILL.
TALKED TO THE OWNER, COMPLETELY STUBBORN ASSHOLE
WOULDN'T CHANGE A THING.
BROUGHT IN SOME BANKER FRIENDS,
THREW SOME ELBOWS, MADE SOME CHANGES.
TWO WEEKS LATER,
EATING OUT OF MY HAND. CLASSIC M & A.
NOW LOOK AT THE PLACE,
MAKING LOTS OF MONEY OFF OUR PAYCHECKS, HUH?
YOU GOT IT. [laughs]
SO HOW DO YOU THINK THE LOCALS FEEL
ABOUT THE CHANGES IN THE MENU?
LOCALS? WHO CARES?
I KNOW, ALL RIGHT? BUT JUST LOOSEN UP!
HE'S A REALLY GOOD GUY,
AND IT'S GONNA BE A GOOD NIGHT.
SO JUST GIVE HIM A CHANCE, ALL RIGHT?
RED OR WHITE? RED.
MAN, YOU ARE GONNA LOVE THESE BITCHES
I HAVE LINED UP FOR US TONIGHT.
HEY, LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION--
HEY, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
HOLD ON A SECOND,
DON'T TELL ME THAT YOU'RE FALLING
FOR THAT MYSTERY CHICK
YOU'VE BEEN HANGING OUT WITH?
NO, NO-- THERE ARE RULES
HERE IN ASIA, BRO.
RULE NUMBER ONE:
ALWAYS WEAR A CONDOM.
RULE NUMBER TWO:
NEVER FALL IN LOVE.
HEY! YO!
YOU'RE A MILLION MILES AWAY.
WE'VE GOT BIG THINGS IN THE WORKS, BRO.
YOU ARE ON YOUR WAY
TO THE MAJOR LEAGUES.
HOW'S THAT SOUND, HUH? HUH?
COME ON, LETS GO CELEBRATE.
HEY, IT'S THAT CHICK THAT WORKS FOR FEI & CHANG!
WHAT'S THAT SAY?UH...
"LOCAL GIRL WORKS HER WAY TO THE TOP
BY SLEEPING WITH THE CEO'S SON."
WHAT A FUCKING SLUT! AH, MAN! PRICELESS!
GET THAT SLUT OUT OF YOUR HEAD.
WHEN THIS IS OVER AND IT FALLS IN HER FACE,
SHE'S GONNA BE GOLD-DIGGING
HER WAY INTO THE NEXT CORPORATE FAMILY.
SO WHAT ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT?
[speaking Cantonese] WHOA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT, YOU THINK YOU'RE ACTUALLY HELPING
THESE PEOPLE BY GIVING THEM CHANGE?
[speaking Cantonese]
LOOK, YOU CRIPPLED HOMELESS FUCK.
GET THE FUCK AWAY FROM ME!
CHILL OUT!
SORRY, BRO. COME ON. LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
[door buzzes]
Both: HEY!
SOMEBODY RING FOR A PARTY?
♪ AND I PUT MYSELF IN A HURRICANE ♪
♪ AND I CLEANSE MYSELF IN THE POURING RAIN ♪
♪ SHE STARES THROUGH YOU
AND YOU FEEL A PULL ♪
♪ LIKE LIGHTNING IN THE NIGHT SO BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ I TAKE MYSELF TO THE HURRICANE ♪
♪ AND I CLEANSE MYSELF
OF ALL THE FEAR AND PAIN ♪
♪ SHE STARES THROUGH ME ♪
JUST DO IT.
♪ AND I FEEL A PULL ♪
♪ LIKE THE FIRE IN THE NIGHT SO BEAUTIFUL ♪
[laughs]
♪ TAKE ME DOWN... ♪
JUST REMEMBER WHO'S GOT YOUR BACK.
♪ ...AND FLY TO YOU ♪
♪ I NEED YOU IN THE MORNING LIGHT ♪
♪ IN THE EYE OF THE STORM ♪
[door buzzes]
GOOD MORNING.
I'M SORRY, WHO ARE--
NATALIE?
NATALIE!
NATALIE! NATALIE, WAIT!
HOW MUCH? HOW MUCH WAS IT WORTH TO YOU?
ARE YOU SERIOUS? I DIDN'T SLEEP WITH HER.
THEN WHAT SHE DOING UP THERE?
HUH, WHAT?
SHE CAME TO STROKE YOUR EGO,
YOU PIECE OF SHIT?!
WHAT ABOUT YOU AND RICHARD, HUH?
WHAT?
YEAH, RICHARD!
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
COME ON, TABLOIDS!
ARE YOU USING ME?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND OF GAME YOU'RE PLAYING!
ARE YOU SERIOUS, CONNER?
IS THAT WHAT YOU REALLY THINK?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO THINK ANYMORE!
OKAY, JUST ANSWER THE FUCKING QUESTION!
ARE YOU FUCKING HIM OR NOT?!
YEAH, YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT TO THINK
BECAUSE YOU'RE TOO BUSY
FOLLOWING DIRECTIONS
AND JUST FOLLOWING OTHER PEOPLE
THAT YOU DON'T HAVE TIME
TO THINK FOR YOURSELF.
LOOK AT YOU. EVERYDAY YOU GO OUT THERE,
YOU PLACE BETS, YOU TAKE RISKS,
BUT YOU CAN'T EVEN TAKE A GAMBLE ON US!
YOU'RE SO SCARED, CONNER.
SO SCARED.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE BETTER THAN THAT.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE TAKING A RISK.
[dialing]
[speaking Cantonese]
A GRISLY SCENE TODAY
AT THE FEI & CHANG SHIPYARD,
WHERE THE BODY OF A MAN HAS BEEN FOUND.
AT THIS STAGE,
THERE ARE UNCONFIRMED REPORTS
THAT THE DEATH HAS BEEN A SUICIDE.
AND OF COURSE THIS IS THE LATEST IN A STRING
OF VERY NEGATIVE PUBLICITY
TO SURROUND THIS COMPANY
WHICH HAS BEEN EXPERIENCING
SEVERE FINANCIAL PROBLEMS.
MORE DETAILS SOON.
[siren wails in distance]
[camera shutters clicking]
SIR, A COMMENT, PLEASE.
[sighs]
I JUST HEARD THE NEWS.
TOUGH BREAK, BRO.
IT HAPPENS TO THE BEST OF US,
AND ALL WE CAN DO IS SHAKE IT OFF
AND MOVE ONTO THE NEXT ONE.
THAT'S WHAT WE DO.
I THOUGHT SHE WAS DIFFERENT.
SHE? WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT, BRO?
NATALIE. YOU HAVEN'T HEARD?
HEARD WHAT?
MR. CHAU, V.P. OF I.T.FOR FEI & CHANG,
WAS FOUND DEAD THIS MORNING...
[sighs]
[dialing]
[beeps]
MICHAEL BAKER, PLEASE.
[crying]
ITS GONNA BE OKAY.
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY. [sniffles]
I PROMISE I'LL MAKE THIS RIGHT.
OKAY? [sniffles]
[sighs]
[sniffles]
HEY, I'M...I'M SORRY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.[sniffles]
WHAT HAPPENED?
NO ONE KNOWS.
THEY JUST FOUND A PRINTED OUT SUICIDE NOTE.
NO WAY.
I'M GONNA BRING SOME TEA UP TO MRS. CHAU.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO LEAVE.
[chuckles] YOU TRICKED ME.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SLEEPING.
YOU KNOW MY,
UH...MY DADDY DIED, TOO.
REALLY? YEAH.
YOU'RE GONNA REMEMBER THIS DAY
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
[sighs] EVERY SINGLE DETAIL.
AND YOU KNOW, ONE DAY...
MAYBE NOT NOW OR TEN YEARS FROM NOW...
YOU'RE GONNA HATE HIM.
YOU'RE GONNA HATE HIM
BECAUSE HE WASN'T THERE...
TO CHEER FOR YOU
AT YOUR CHAMPIONSHIP BASEBALL GAME,
OR HEAR YOU GIVE
YOUR VALEDICTORIAN SPEECH
AT YOUR HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATION.
AND YOU'RE...
YOU'RE GONNA FEEL LIKE ANYTHING YOU DO...
WON'T BE GOOD ENOUGH...
THAT ANYTHING YOU DO...
WON'T MATTER...
'CAUSE IT WON'T BRING HIM BACK.
AND ONE DAY...
YOU'LL UNDERSTAND.
HOLD ON TO THAT FOR ME.
COME ON, WE GOTTA GO.
EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH, FINE.
LISTEN UH, BUNCH OF US ARE GATHERING
FOR DRINKS DOWNSTAIRS IF YOU WANT TO JOIN.
UH, GOT A LOT OF WORK. I'LL TRY TO JOIN, THOUGH.
OKAY, BRO.
[door shuts]
[dialing]
YEAH, ANDY, I FOUND THE SHORT TRANSACTIONS,
BUT THEY'RE LOCKED.
FUCK! UH...
YOU'RE GONNA TO HAVE TO ACCESS THEM
ON QUENTIN'S COMPUTER.
OKAY.
[door opens]
BLOODY SECOND TIME THIS WEEK...
WHAT'S UP, CONNER?
UH, HEY, UM...
YOU KNOW, I LEFT MY NOTEBOOK IN THERE.
YOU WOULDN'T BY CHANCE
KNOW QUENTIN'S CODE?
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH. SURE, SURE.
I SAW HIM PUNCH IT IN ONCE
FROM OVER THERE.
[both chuckle]
ALL RIGHT, LET ME REMEMBER...
[beeps]
BINGO. NOT VERY HARD, IS IT?
NOT AS IF IT'S 'SLUT' OR SOMETHING.
[both chuckle]
SERIOUSLY, MAN, HE'S GOT WEIRD TASTE IN ART.
SORRY, HAVE YOU FOUND
WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR?
I CAN'T FIND IT, BUT, UM, THANKS ANYWAYS.
NO WORRIES.
SO YOU GONNA COME DOWNSTAIRS LATER ON
AND HAVE A FEW BEVIES WITH THE LADS?
RIGHT, UH, YEAH, I HEARD.
I GOT A LOT OF STUFF TO DO.
SO... I'LL TRY.
YOU OKAY, MATE?
YEAH, FINE.
ALL RIGHT, MATE.
SEE YOU LATER, YEAH? YEAH.
DON'T WORK TOO HARD! OKAY.
[door opens and closes]
[beeps]
FUCK, THERE'S A LOGIN.
QUENTIN'S NOT THE BRIGHTEST. THINK LIKE HIM.
BARS, CHICKS, NUMBERS,
INSIDE JOKES, WHATEVER.
ONE SECOND.
SLUT.
OKAY, I'M IN.
COPYING IT RIGHT NOW.
HEY, MAN.
[beeps]
YOU COMING?
SORRY, WHAT?
I SAID, ARE YOU COMING?
YOU KNOW WHAT? UH...
YEAH, I DON'T THINK IT'S GONNA WORK OUT.
I JUST GOT WAY TOO MUCH WORK.
IT'S NOT THE SAME WITHOUT YOU, BRO.
YEAH, BUT YOU KNOW, I THINK
IT'S GONNA BE AN ALL-NIGHTER.
YOU SURE?
POSITIVE, THANKS.
EVERYTHING'S ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, REALLY. NEXT TIME.
OKAY.
[door opens and closes]
[sighs]
[beeps]
OKAY, I THINK IT FINISHED COPYING.
FUCK, BUT THERE'S NO NAMES.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED SOMEBODY
AT FEI & CHANG
TO MATCH THE TRANSACTION NUMBERS.
FUCK!
HEY, JAMES. HEY, BEAUTIFUL.
HEY! WHAT ARE YOU DOING, MATE?
DON'T BE CRACKING ON MY BIRD!
CONNER FIND HIS NOTEBOOK?
WHAT NOTEBOOK?
HE SAID HE LEFT IT IN YOUR OFFICE.
[siren wails in distance]
YOU LUCK BOX.
GET OFF ME.
[chuckles] LET HIM GO.
[sighs]
WE NEED TO TALK.
TALKING IS SO BLASé.
BLAH BLAH BLAH.
YOU AMERICAN'S LOVE TO TALK.
LOOK, RICHARD--
NO, YOU LOOK.
YOU WANT TO STAY, THEN PUT
YOUR BLOOD MONEY WHERE YOUR MOUTH IS.
FINE.
AH, NOW DOESN'T THAT
FEEL MUCH BETTER?
MONEY, WEALTH, FORTUNE.
CONNER, WHO CARES?
YOUR WESTERN PHILOSOPHY
IS THE ONE WITH THE MOST TOYS WINS.
BUT CAN'T YOU SEE?
NOT THIS TIME, MR. AMERICA. NOT THIS TIME.
WE ALL LOSE!
I KNOW WE HAVEN'T SEEN EYE TO EYE,
BUT I CAN HELP YOU.
I JUST NEED TO MATCH THESE RECORDS
WITH YOUR FINANCIAL DATA
TO GET EVIDENCE ON WHO IS MAKING
SHORT TRADES ON YOUR COMPANY.
AND WHY SHOULD I LISTEN TO YOU NOW?
SUDDENLY YOU CARE
ABOUT HELPING MY COMPANY?
I DON'T GIVE A SHIT ABOUT YOUR COMPANY.
MR. CHAU--
DON'T YOU EVEN SAY HIS NAME!
MR. CHAU IS DEAD! DON'T YOU...EVEN SAY HIS NAME!
[breathing heavily]
ALL IN.
I FOLD.
FLIP IT.
YOU SURE YOU WANT TO DO THIS?
IF YOU'RE NOT GAMBLING, YOU'RE NOT LIVING.
[bang]
OKAY, I'M GONNA GO CHECK ON THIS REAL QUICK.
CONNER!
NO! NO!
I'M NOT GOING IN THE CLOSET!
FUCKERS! GET OVER HERE!
Richard:YOU'RE SO AMERICAN.
YOU'RE THE BLIND LEADING THE BLIND.
Donald: WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT FAMILY, MR. LEE?
Natalie: YOU'RE SO SCARED, CONNER. SO SCARED.
[grunting]
[groans]
NO! NO! NO! NO! [screams]
FOR THE LAST FIVE YEARS. WHAT ABOUT ASIA?
WE GOT A GUY SET UP IN HONG KONG.
REAL SMART. KNOWS HIS STUFF.
[phone vibrates]
THAT'S HIM RIGHT NOW.
YEAH?
WE CREATE EVENTS.
[groaning]
[continues groaning]
[chuckles]
[groaning]
YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHY? WHY?!
WHY WHAT?
YOU USED ME!
YEAH, I DID.
MICHAEL? HE'S BEEN PUSHING
FOR THE POISON PILL THIS WHOLE TIME.
THEY'RE FINALLY GONNA GO THROUGH WITH IT.
THE STOCK PRICE WILL DROP AND OUR SHORT POSITIONS
WILL FAR OUTDO YOUR BUY POSITIONS.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE
500 MILLION, GUARANTEED!
FIVE HUNDRED MILLION? FIVE HUNDRED
FUCKING MILLION?! WHO FUCKING CARES?!
THIS IS NOT A GAME, QUENTIN!
OH, IT'S ALL A GAME!
AND YOU PLAYED IT LIKE A CHAMP!
ALL THOSE LETTER YOU WROTE?
THE AUDITORS, THE PRESS?
IT'S ALL PART OF IT.
COME ON, CONNER.
IT'S EASIER TO MAKE A STOCK PRICE GO DOWN
THAN MAKE IT GO UP, ISN'T IT?
AND BESIDES, WHO REALLY LOSES?
MR. CHAU?
WAS HE A FUCKING NUMBER TO YOU?!
YEAH, THAT'S...
WHY'D YOU FUCKING DO IT, MAN?! EASY, BRO.
IF HIS OWN SIDE WANTS TO TAKE HIM OUT,
I CAN'T HELP THAT.
THAT'S RIGHT. CHECK YOUR FACTS.
MARK WOULD NEVER LET THIS FUCKING HAPPEN!
MARK? YEAH, MARK!
IT WAS HIS IDEA TO SEND YOU
OUT HERE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
OH, YOU THOUGHT YOU HAD FRIENDS?
YOU AIN'T GOT
NO MOTHERFUCKING FRIENDS.
I WAS YOUR FRIEND!
YOU GOT MY BACK, RIGHT, BRO?
HUH? YOU CHICKEN SHIT!
YOU PIECE OF SHIT!
COME ON! COME ON!
[groans] OH! OUCH!
THAT MUST HAVE HURT, HUH?
YOU WANT A PIECE, CONNER? THAT'S RIGHT.
[grunts] MISSED!
[grunts] BOO YA!
[groans]
IN WHAT WORLD WERE YOU LIVING IN
THAT YOU THOUGHT YOU COULD BEAT ME? ME!
LOOK AT ME.
THIS IS MY CITY!
[grunting]
[chuckles]
[groans]
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BE MY BOY.
INSTEAD YOU END UP BEING MY BITCH!
HEY, QUENTIN...
DIU LE LO MO!
NO, YOU'RE THE ONE THAT'S FUCKED.
OH, WELL, LOOK, YOUR BOYFRIEND
CAME TO RESCUE YOU.
[groans]
ENOUGH!
HEY, RICH, WHAT UP YO?
COME TO RESCUE
THIS PRETTY PIECE OF ASS?
WELL, I TELL YOU WHAT,
YOU CAN HAVE IT
AFTER I FINISH KICKING THE SHIT OUT OF IT.
UNTIL THEN, IT'S NONE
OF YOUR FUCKING BUSINESS.
INTERESTING USE OF WORDS.
IT'S THE ONE THING THAT
YOU HAVEN'T LEARNED, QUENTIN...
THAT THERE ARE SOME THINGS
THAT ARE MORE IMPORTANT THAN BUSINESS.
YEAH? AND WHAT'S THAT,
YOU ASS FUCKER?
LIKE LOYALTY.
[speaking Cantonese]
[groans]
ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU REALLY ARE A DUMB AMERICAN.
[grunting]
[groans]
Michael: SO, I JUST NEED YOU TO SIGN HERE...
RIGHT HERE...
AND FINALLY RIGHT HERE.
[phone vibrates]
YEAH?
LET ME TALK TO DONALD.
OH, UH... DONALD IS BUSY.
FUCK.
WHO WAS THAT?
EH... GO ON.
ALL RIGHT, SO FINALLY HERE,
AND RIGHT HERE AS WELL.
DON'T SIGN THOSE DOCUMENTS!
WHAT'S GOING ON? RICHARD!
RICHARD WAS WORKING
ON A COMPUTER SYSTEM,
ONE THAT WOULD REVOLUTIONIZE THE INDUSTRY
AND SAVE YOUR COMPANY.
THIS IS LUDICROUS!
IS IT, MICHAEL?
YOU GUYS KNOW EACH OTHER?
MR. CHAU WAS DESIGNING THE SYSTEM.
RICHARD AND I HAVE BEEN WORKING ON A WAY
TO PRESENT THIS TO YOU, MR. CHANG.
OH, I'VE HEARD ENOUGH!
OH, IT GETS BETTER.
INTRODUCING THE FEI & CHANG
INTERNAL SOCIAL NETWORK.
SEE, EACH EMPLOYEE
GETS THEIR OWN ACCOUNT,
ONE WHERE THEY CANNOT ONLY
KEEP TABS ON ONE ANOTHER,
SHARE WORK ITEMS,
BUT GETS DAILY POINTS
FOR THE GOOD WORK THAT THEY'VE DONE.
AND AT THE END OF EACH QUARTER
THEY CAN TRADE IN THOSE POINTS FOR GIFTS,
OR GAMBLE IT AWAY
FOR EVEN HIGHER REWARDS.
ONLY A VIDEO GAME. MAKES NO SENSE.
NO SENSE TO SOMEONE
WHO'S NEXT IN LINE TO BE CEO.
SEE, THAT WAS THE PIECE OF THE PUZZLE
THAT I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND--
HOW MICHAEL AND QUENTIN WERE GOING
TO CONVINCE YOU TO TAKE THE POISON PILL.
AND IT TOOK RICHARD HERE
TELLING ME HOW MUCH
OF AN AMERICAN I AM FOR ME TO REALIZE.
SEE, I TAKE EVERYTHING AT FACE VALUE,
BELIEVE WHATEVER I'M FED.
MARK SAW THAT IN ME AND THAT'S WHY
HE SENT ME OUT HERE.
YOU ARE DOING EXACTLY
WHAT YOU SHOULD BE DOING.
TO SHAKE IT UP A LITTLE.
HE THOUGHT I COULD BE BOUGHT.
SO, SHORT POSITIONS,
FROM INSIDE FEI & CHANG
FROM OFFSHORE ACCOUNTS--
ACCOUNTS THAT ARE LINKED TO VICTOR.
QUENTIN TOLD US EVERYTHING.
THIS IS OUTRAGEOUS!
WHY'D YOU KILL MR. CHAU, VICTOR?
WAS IT BECAUSE HE WAS BUILDING THE SYSTEM
THAT WOULD EXPOSE YOU? HMM?
MAYBE IT WAS BECAUSE YOU FINALLY REALIZED
YOU WOULD NEVER BECOME CEO.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
AND I THOUGHT YOU WERE
ALL ABOUT FAMILY, VICTOR.
I CAN'T STAND THIS!
WHY'D YOU KILL MR. CHAU, VICTOR?
NO.
WHY DID YOU KILL HIM? HUH?
HE HAD A SON!
WHY DID YOU KILL MR. CHAU?!
WHY DID YOU KILL HIM, HUH?!
I DID IT FOR THE FAMILY!
THE COMPANY WAS BEING
RUN DOWN TO THE GROUND.
YOU THINK A LITTLE COMPUTER GAME
WAS GOING TO SOLVE OUR PROBLEMS?
NO!
THIS COMPANY NEEDS REAL LEADERSHIP!
I LOVE WHAT FATHER LEFT TO US
TOO MUCH TO SEE IT FAIL!
I DID IT-- I DID IT FOR THE FAMILY.
I DID IT FOR THE FAMILY!
[sobbing]
I...
[sighs]
NATALIE, CAN YOU--
I'M ON IT, MR. CHANG.
THANK YOU.
SO, CONNER, LOOKS LIKE YOU KNOW
MY COMPANY BETTER THAN I DO.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
I SHOULD KNOW ABOUT?
IT'S ALL RIGHT, SON.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY ANYTHING.
I SHOULD HAVE NEVER DOUBTED YOU.
[sighs]
[dialing]
[beeps]
HEY, CONNER.
SURPRISED TO HEAR FROM ME?
WELL, I ALWAYS SAID
YOU HAD YOUR FATHER'S EDGE.
IT'S OVER.
OH, NO, IT'S NOT OVER, KID.
IT'S JUST POSTPONED.
I KNOW ABOUT YOUR POSITIONS
IN FEI & CHANG.
I KNOW THAT YOU WERE
THE ONE TO SET ME UP.
OH, YOU'RE DAMN RIGHT
I WAS SETTING YOU UP!
I WAS SETTING YOU UP FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE,
YOU UNGRATEFUL SHIT!
I WAS GONNA BRING YOU IN!
I WAS GIVING YOU EVERYTHING!
YOU GAVE ME NOTHING AND NOW
YOU'VE LOST IT ALL.
I BUILT THIS FUND FROM NOTHING,
I'LL DO IT AGAIN.
YOU WANNA BET?
THE SFC ARE INVESTIGATING.
QUENTIN AND VICTOR-- CONFESSING.
MARK, YOU'RE FINISHED.
I GUESS I BECAME THE MAN
I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE AFTER ALL.
[sighs]
ARE YOU READY TO GO?
JUST ONE MORE CALL TO MAKE.
HEY, MOM? YEAH, IT'S ME...
♪ AND I PUT MYSELF IN A HURRICANE ♪
♪ AND I CLEANSE MYSELF
IN THE POURING RAIN ♪
♪ SHE STARES THROUGH YOU ♪
♪ AND YOU FEEL A PULL ♪
♪ LIKE LIGHTNING IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ SO BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ I TAKE MYSELF TO THE HURRICANE ♪
♪ AND I CLEANSE MYSELF
OF ALL THE FEAR AND PAIN ♪
♪ SHE STARES THROUGH ME
AND I FEEL A PULL ♪
♪ LIKE THE FIRE IN THE NIGHT SO BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ TAKE ME DOWN, I NEED YOUR POWER ♪
♪ I LIFT MY ARMS AND FLY TO YOU ♪
♪ I NEED YOU IN THE MORNING ♪
♪ I NEED YOU ALL NIGHT ♪
♪ I NEED YOU IN THE MORNING LIGHT ♪
♪ IN THE EYE OF THE STORM ♪
♪ AND I STEAL MYSELF
TO THE EYE OF THE STORM ♪
♪ THE COVER FALLS
LIKE A NEW DAY'S DAWN ♪
♪ AND SHE SMILES AT ME
AS I FEEL A PULL ♪
♪ LIKE A FIRE IN THE NIGHT SO BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ I WILL HOLD YOU,KEEP YOU SAFE ♪
♪ OH, TILL THE HURRICANE IS GONE NOW ♪
♪ TILL THE HURRICANE IS GONE NOW, BABY ♪
♪ I WILL HOLD YOU, KEEP YOU SAFE ♪
♪ OH, TILL THE HURRICANE IS GONE NOW, BABY ♪
♪ TILL THE HURRICANE IS GONE NOW,
GONE NOW ♪
♪ I WILL HOLD YOU, KEEP YOU SAFE ♪
♪ OH, TILL THE HURRICANE IS GONE NOW, BABY ♪
♪ TILL THE HURRICANE IS GONE NOW,
GONE NOW ♪
♪ I WILL HOLD YOU,KEEP YOU SAFE ♪
♪ IT'S THE EYE OF THE STORM ♪